[
    {
        "front": "しんぱい（する）\n「心配」",
        "back": "to worry",
        "chapter": "N4 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "ばかり",
        "back": "only, just",
        "chapter": "N4 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "かける",
        "back": "to make, to cause",
        "chapter": "N4 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "クラシック（な）",
        "back": "classical",
        "chapter": "N4 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "コンサート",
        "back": "concert",
        "chapter": "N4 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうみ\n「興味」",
        "back": "interest",
        "chapter": "N4 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "なかなか～ない",
        "back": "seldom; to have difficulty",
        "chapter": "N4 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "きかい\n「機会」",
        "back": "chance",
        "chapter": "N4 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "チケット",
        "back": "ticket",
        "chapter": "N4 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "びじゅつかん\n「美術館」",
        "back": "art museum",
        "chapter": "N4 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "てんらんかい\n「展覧会」",
        "back": "exhibition",
        "chapter": "N4 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひらく\n「開く」",
        "back": "to hold",
        "chapter": "N4 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "すばらしい",
        "back": "wonderful",
        "chapter": "N4 C9"
    }
]